(Howard:)It means after we play handball,
I'm showering at home.
(Sheldon:)Good morning, Friend Howard.
(Sheldon:)Friend Raj.
(Sheldon:)I see you gentlemen
are enjoying beverages.
(Sheldon:)Perhaps they would taste better
out of these.
"World's Greatest
Astrophysicist"?
(Sheldon:)Don't thank me. You earned it.
"Howard Wolowitz."
(Howard:)Why not
"World's Greatest Engineer"?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Sheldon:)I typed that
into the label maker,
(Sheldon:)but I just couldn't press enter.
(Sheldon:)Now down to business.
(Sheldon:)What would it take for you
to abandon Leonard
(Sheldon:)and join me in a rival company?
(Sheldon:)Unless, of course,
the mugs are sufficient,
(Sheldon:)in which case, welcome aboard.
(Howard:)We're not quitting on Leonard.
(Sheldon:)I understand.
Your loyalty is admirable.
(Sheldon:)But what if I were
to up the ante?
(Raj:)What are you talking about?
(Sheldon:)Monogrammed key chains